


const Questions = [
    {
      question: "Who is India's Prime Minister",
      option1: "Narendra Modi",
      option2: "Rahul Gandhi",
      option3: "Mamata Banerjee",
      option4: "Chandrababu Naidu",
      answer: "Narendra Modi",
      time: 20,
      key: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is India's President",
      option1: "Droupadi Murmu",
      option2: "sonia gandhi",
      option3: "ajay ",
      option4: "Eknath Shinde",
      answer: "Droupadi Murmu",
      time: 30,
      key: 2,
    },   {
        question: "Who is India's Defence Minister",
        option1: "Amit Shah",
        option2: "Jay shah",
        option3: "Rajnath Singh",
        option4: "Nirmala Sitharaman",
        answer: "Rajnath Singh",
        time: 30,
        key: 3,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Finance Minister",
        option1: "Kiren Rijiju",
        option2: "Ravi Kishan",
        option3: "Ram Mohan Naidu ",
        option4: "Nirmala Sitharaman",
        answer: "Nirmala Sitharaman",
        time: 30,
        key: 4,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Civil Aviation Minister",
        option1: "Raghunandan Rao",
        option2: "Bandi Sanjay",
        option3: "Smriti Irani ",
        option4: "Ram Mohan Naidu",
        answer: "Ram Mohan Naidu",
        time: 30,
        key: 5,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Agriculture Minister",
        option1: "Kiran Reddy",
        option2: "Jayant Sinha",
        option3: "Shivraj Singh Chouhan",
        option4: "Nitin Gadkari",
        answer: "Shivraj Singh Chouhan",
        time: 30,
        key: 6,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Transport Minister",
        option1: "Nitin Gadkari",
        option2: "Jiten Ram Manjhi",
        option3: "Akhilesh Yadav",
        option4: "Subroto Chaterjee",
        answer: "Nitin Gadkari",
        time: 30,
        key: 7,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Jal Shakti Minister",
        option1: "Ajit Pawar",
        option2: "Shatrughan Sinha",
        option3: " Om Birla",
        option4: "Gajendra Singh Shekhawat",
        answer: "Gajendra Singh Shekhawat",
        time: 30,
        key: 8,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Heavy Industries Minister",
        option1: "HD Kumaraswamy",
        option2: "DK ShivaKumar ",
        option3: "Siddaramaiah ",
        option4: "Devendra Fadnavis",
        answer: "HD Kumaraswamy",
        time: 30,
        key: 9,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Environment Minister",
        option1: "Ajit Pawar",
        option2: "Bhupendra Yadav",
        option3: "Mallikarjun Kharge ",
        option4: "Ram",
        answer: "Bhupendra Yadav",
        time: 30,
        key: 10,
      }, {
        question: "Who is India's Parliamentary Affairs Minister",
        option1: "Nitish Kumar",
        option2: "MK Stalin",
        option3: "Prahlad Joshi",
        option4: "Ashwini Vaishnaw",
        answer: "Prahlad Joshi",
        time: 30,
        key: 11,
      }
  ]

  export default Questions